MITCHELL BOUMELHEM

mitchellboumelhem@gmail.com

0401185859

Baulkham Hills, NSW, 2153

LINKS

Portfolio

mjboumelhem.com

GitHub

https://github.com/MTK-96

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mitchell-boumelhem-40a651188/

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaSvript
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Figma

EDUCATION

High School Diploma, Crestwood High School

January 2009 - September 2014

Modern JavaScript from the beginning (Udemy)

August 2019 - November 2019

Modern HTML & CSS from the beginning (Udemy)

June 2020 - September 2020

SUMMARY

Self-taught Front-End Web Developer based in Sydney, New South Wales. I have a passion for creating beautiful, responsive and dynamic websites. I have been actively learning and coding since mid-2019, tailoring my skills and knowledge to create excellent user experiences.

CAREER HISTORY

Games Coordinator, JB HI-FI PTY LTD

February 2014 - Present

- Sales / Customer Service
- Merchandising
- Stock Control & Budgets

Crew Trainer, Hungry Jacks

September 2012 - August 2014

- Food Service preparation
- Crew Training
- Customer Service

REFERENCES

Ryan Smith - Sales Manager - JB HI-FI PTY LTD 0422 073 890

Andre Clemente - Media Manager - JB HI-FI PTY LTD 0401 579 478